Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of War and Peace Movements Serials TAM.757
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- International Conference for Solidarity with the People of Vietnam Against US Imperialist Aggression and for the Defense of Peace: Bureau of the International Conference for Solidarity with the People of Vietnam Against US Imperialist Aggression and for the Defense of Peace, Hanoi, Vietnam, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 17, Box 27, Folder 15)
- International Peace Studies Newsletter: Center for Peace Studies, Akron, OH, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- International Workcamper: Volunteers for Peace, Inc., Belmont, VT, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Issues: Fund for Peace, Washington, DC, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- IVth Congress of Vietnamese Women: Basic Documents: Viet Nam Women's Union, Hanoi, Vietnam, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Jackrabbit News: The Jackrabbit News, Yakima, WA, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Jailbreak: High School Youth Against War and Fascism, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Jewish Peace Fellowship: Jewish Peace Fellowship, Nyack, NY, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Jewish Women's Peace Bulletin: Jewish Women's Committee to End the Occupation of the West Bank and Gaza, New York, NY, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Jobs With Peace!: National Jobs with Peace Campaign, Boston, MA, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Journal of the Resistance: New England Resistance, Boston, MA, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- July 2nd Mobilizer: Ad Hoc Committee for July 2 Emergency Mobilization, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- June 12th News: June 12th Rally Committee, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- June Twelfth: June 12th Rally Committee, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Just Peace: Florida Coalition for Peace & Justice, Orlando, FL, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Kakkin News: National Council for Peace and Against Nuclear Weapons, Tokyo, Japan, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Kampuchea Bulletin: Kampuchea Support Committee, New York, NY, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5, Box 27, Folder 18)
- Kapinatyolainen: Kapinatyolainen, Helsinki, Finland, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Keep America Out of War Congress News: New York City Committee, New York, NY, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Keep Nuclear Weapons Out of New York Harbor!: Coalition for a Nuclear Free Harbor, New York, NY, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Kids Meeting Kids Can Make a Difference: Kids Meeting Kids can Make A Difference, New York, NY, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Kill for Peace Again: Strolling Dog Press, New York, NY, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Killeen/Ft. Hood Area Chapter Newsletter: Vietnam Veterans Against the War, Killeen, TX, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Kitty Litter: Voices of the Cockiest Hawks: Harbor Project, San Diego, CA, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Kontakt: Larry Swingle / Rosa Palinkas, West Germany, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- La Grande guerre par les artistes: Berger-Levrault et Georges Cres and Co., Paris, France, 1914-1916 (Box 21, Folder 2-6)
- la Paz/Peace News: la Paz/Peace News, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- La Voie de la paix: L'Union Pacifiste de France, Paris, France, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Lag Rag: Livermore Action Group, Berkeley, CA, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Lane County Nuclear News Bureau: CALS, Eugene, OR, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 9-11)
- Le Reveil des combattants: L'association republicaine des anciens combattants, Paris, France, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Legislative Alert: Women's International League for Peace & Freedom, Washington, DC, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Legislative Update: Coalition to Stop Funding the War, Washington, DC, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Les juristes prennent position contre l'experimentation et l'utilisation des armes atomiques / Lawyers take position against experiments and use of atomic weapons: Association Internationale des Juristes Democrates, Brussels, Belgium, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Let Iraq Live: Syracuse Peace Council & Community Media Action Group, Syracuse, NY, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Letter from Robert A. Seeley of CCCO: CCCO / A National Agency for Military and Draft Counseling, San Francisco, CA, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- LINK: American Servicemens Union, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Lock 'N' Load: Vietnam Veterans Against the War/Winter Soldier Organization, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 20, Box 21, Folder 13)
- Long Island Duck: Long Island Free Press, Carle Place, NY, Undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
- LU Links Um!: Plambeck & Co Printing and Publishing, Dortmund, Germany, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- MAC: The Military and the Community: MAC, Philadelphia, PA, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- March for Peace: National Student Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- May Flowers, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Medical Aid for Indochina: Indochina Resource Center, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Mellow Dove: Peace and Freedom Party, Long Beach, CA, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Metro Call to Action: Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, New York, NY, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Middle East Newsletter: World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 24, Box 27, Folder 19)
- Mideast Crisis Weekly: Lexington, KY, Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Midwest Pacifist Commentator: Midwest Pacifist Center / Bradford Lyttle, Chicago, IL, 1986-1991 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Midwest SPU Digest: Student Peace Union, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Milwaukee Advocate: Jobs with Peace, Milwaukee, WI, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Mission Hill Vietnam Bulletin: Mission Hill Vietnam Committee, unknown, Undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Mission to Hanoi: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Mobilization for Survival Letter and Leaflets: Mobilization for Survival of New York, Inc., New York, NY, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Movement Escalates to Stop Nuclear Power Rise Up...Or Melt Down!: Revolutionary Student Brigade, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Movin' Together: People's Coalition for Peace & Justice, New York, NY, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
- Muste Notes: A.J. Muste Memorial Institute, New York, NY, 1998-2007 (Box 8, Folder 32, Box 27, Folder 21)
- N.Y. Mobilizer: Mobilization for Survival / NY, New York, NY, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1, Box 27, Folder 22)
- N.Y.C.A.N.G. Post: New York City Anti-Nuclear Group, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- National Guard in Central America and Other Local Military Connections Oraganization Guide: National Guard Clearing House, St. Louis, MO, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
- National Network for Direct Action: Fellowship of Reconciliation, Nayac, NY, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- National Peace Academy Campaign Campaign Update: National Peace Academy Campaign, Washington, DC, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Neighbors United for Peace: Neighbors United for Peace, Michigan, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Network: New York State Non-Nuclear Network, New York, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Network News: National Anti-Draft Network of YAWF, New York, NY, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Network News: Queens Network for Peace and Justice, Flushing, NY, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Networks: Newsletter of the L.I. Network for Peace and Justice: Long Island Network for Peace and Justice, Westbury, NY, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- New Abolitionist: Nuclear Free America, Baltimore, MD, 1984-1987 (Box 22, Folder 7-9, Box 9, Folder 11, Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 14)
- New Education and the Future of Peace: American Association for Jewish Education, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- New England Briefs for Middle East Peacework: American Friends Service Committee, Cambridge, MA, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- New Jersey Peace Action Forty-second Annual Dinner: New Jersey Peace Action, Cedar Grove, NJ, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- New Jersey Peacemaker: New Jersey Peace Action and New Jersey Peace Action Education Fund, Montclair, NJ, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 15-17)
- New Manhattan Project Newsletter: American Friends Service Committee, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- New Mobilizer: New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, Washington, DC, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- New People: Thomas Merton Center, Pittsburgh, PA, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 19, Box 22, Folder 11)
- New Year One: Year One / Jonah House, Baltimore, MD, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 20, Box 27, Folder 23)
- News: American Peace Mobilization, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- News Bulletin Queens Women Strike for Peace: Women Strike for Peace, Flushing, NY, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- News from South Vietnam: Commission of Information of SVNNFL, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- News from Vietnam: Association of Vietnamese Patriots in Canada, Montreal, Quebec, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
- News Notes: Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 22-24, Box 27, Folder 24)
- News Notes: Disciples Peace Fellowship, Indianapolis, IN, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- News of the Anti-Drafters: End The Draft, Brooklyn, NY, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Newsletter: American Friends Service Committee, Chicago, IL, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Newsletter: Brooklyn Heights SANE/FREEZE, Brooklyn, NY, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Newsletter: Conference on Peace Research in History, Garden City, NY, 1973-1985 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Newsletter: Grandmothers for Peace, Sacramento, CA, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Newsletter: The Laywer's Committee on Nuclear Policy, New York, NY, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Newsletter: United States Congress Against War, New York, NY, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Newsletter: Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, New York Metropolitan Branch, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Newsletter: Seattle Women Act for Peace, Seattle, WA, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Newswire: Military Families Support Network, Milwaukee, WI, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- No Business as Usual: NBAU Action Network, San Francisco, CA, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 36-37)
- No-Register Guard: Coalition Opposing Registration and the Draft (CORD), Undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Nonviolent: War Resisters League, New York, NY, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- North Atlantic Network Newsetter: North Atlantic Network, Oslo, Norway, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- North Vietnamese Medicine Facing the Trial of War: Vietnamese Studies, Hanoi, Vietnam, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Northeast Ohio Peace and Justice Calendar: American Friends Service Committee, Akron, OH, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Northern Sun News: Northern Sun Alliance, Minneapolis, MN, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 42-43, Box 22, Folder 16, Box 27, Folder 25)
- Northwest Nuclear Xchange: Northwest Nuclear Xchange, Seattle, WA, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 18-20)
- Notes on Germany: Society for the Prevention of World War III, Inc., New York, NY, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Nouvelles du Laos: Bureau d'information du front patriotique lao a hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Nuclear Free America- Assorted Materials: Nuclear Free America, Baltimore, MD, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Nuclear Reactions: Nuclear Disarment Movement, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Nuclear War Prevention Kit: Center for Defense Information, Washington, DC, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Nucleus: Union of Concerned Scientists, Cambridge, MA, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Nukewatch Newsletter: The Progressive Foundation, Madison, WI, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- NY Mobe Update: New York Mobilization for Survival, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
- NY Mobilizer: Mobilization for Survival/NY, New York, NY, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- NY Network Calendar: NY Peace Network, New York, NY, 1987-1990 (Box 22, Folder 23-24, Box 10, Folder 5)
- NYU US Out of the Gulf Coalition Newsletter: NYU US Out of the Gulf Coalition, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Off the Brass: Portsmouth Area Service People and Vietnam Veterans Against the War, Portsmouth, NH, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Offul Times: Omaha Military Project, Omaha, NE, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Oklahoma Peace Strategy: The Peace House, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1996 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 15)
- On Beyond War: Beyond War, Palo Alto, CA, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- On Guard: Citizen Soldier, New York, NY, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 9, Box 23, Folder 2-3, Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 16)
- On the Ground: Community Media Action Group, Syracuse, NY, circa 2000s (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 17)
- One World: World Association of World Federalists, Chicago, IL, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Opposition: Air War: Campaign End the Air War, Voluntown, CT, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Our Nuclear Future: A Congressional Briefing on the Hazards of Nuclear Weapons and Power Production: Friends Committee on National Legislation/Fellowship of Reconciliation/American Friends Service Committee, Nyack, NY/Denver, CO, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Our Times: Our Times, Cambridge, MA, Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
- P/LS News and Comment: NH Action for Peace & Lasting Security, Concord, NH, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Pacific News Service: Pacific News Service, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Pacific Peacemaker: Pacific Peacemaker Foundation, Seattle, WA, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Pagans for Peace Newsletter: Pagans for Peace Network, Toronto, Ontario, Undated (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
- Paix et Securite: Institut Canadien Pour La Paix et La Securite Internationales, Ottawa, Ontario, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- PAX: Utges av Svenska Fredsoch Skiljedomsforeningen, Stockholm, Sweden, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Payback: VMFA-323, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Peace: The American Pax Society, New York, NY, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Peace: Black P. Stone Nation, Chicago, IL, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Peace: A World Review: The Bureau of the World Peace Council, Paris, France, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Peace & Freedom: US Section of the Women's International League for Peace & Freedom, Philadelphia, PA, 1986-1999 (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
- Peace & Freedom Council Newsletter: Peace & Freedom Council, Cotati, CA, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Peace Action: Peace Action Education Fund, Washington, DC, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Peace and Democracy News: Campaign for Peace and Democracy/East and West, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Peace and Freedom National Organizer: Peace & Freedom National Organizing Committee, Berkeley, CA, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Peace and Freedom National Organizer: Peace and Freedom Party, Chicago, IL, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Peace and Freedom Organizer: Peace and Freedom Party, San Francisco, CA, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Peace and Freedom Partisan: Peace and Freedom Party, San Jose, CA, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 11-12)
- Peace and Freedom Review: Peace and Freedom Party, San Francisco, CA, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Peace and Justice: Peace Action Council (PCPJ), Los Angeles, CA, Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Peace and Solidarity: Peace and Solidarity Project, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Peace Call: Ed Pearl, Los Angeles, CA, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Peace Developments: Newsletter of the Peace Development Fund: Peace Development Fund, Amherst, MA, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Peace Digest: Peace Magazine / Edward A. Balinski, Atlantic City, NJ, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Peace Education Bulletin: American Friends Service Committee, Philadelphia, PA, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Peace Issues: War Resisters League, New York, NY, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Peace Lines: National Women Strike for Peace, Philadelphia, PA, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Peace Magazine: Peace Magazine, Toronto, Ontario, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Peace Makers: Peace Center of Central Jersey, Highland Park, NJ, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Peace News: American Friends Service Committee, Inc., San Antonio, TX, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Peace News: Corona E. Elmhurst Jackson Heights Peace Committee, Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Peace News Bulletin: World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Peace News Pamphlet: Peace News Ltd., London, UK, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Peace News Wire: Peace Information Service, San Francisco, CA, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Peace Now: Peace Now Educational Fund, New York, NY, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Peace Now News: Americans for Peace Now, Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Peace Release: Peace Park Anti-Nuclear Vigil, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Peace Talk: New York Peace Council, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 39, Box 23, Folder 14-15)
- Peace Thru Justice: Mercy Sisters, Louisville, KY, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Peace Times: Vietnam Moratorium Committee, Washington, DC, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Peace Wave News: Peace Wave Action Committee, Tokyo, Japan, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Peaceful Pieces: The Boise Peace Quilt Project, Boise, ID, Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Peaceletter: Peace Resource Center of Santa Barbara, Santa Barbara, CA, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- PeaceSmith House Newsletter: PeaceSmith House, Inc., Massapequa, NY, Undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
- PeaceVision Newsletter: PeaceVision, Ann Arbor, MI, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- PeaceWatch: United States Institute of Peace, Washington, DC, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Peaceways: Central Kentucky Council for Peace and Justice, Lexington, KY, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Pentagon Paper: Pentagon Papers Peace Project, Los Angeles, CA, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 17-19)
- People of Vietnam Will Triumph! The U.S. Aggressors Will Be Defeated!: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- People's Path to Peace, Equality, Socialism: Communist Party of Minnesota and the Dakotas, Minneapolis, MN, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Peoples Anti-War Mobilizers Notes: People's Anti-War Mobilization, New York, NY, Undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Pershing Plowshares Newsletter: Pershing Plowshares Support Committee, Orlando, FL, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Persian Gulf Update: Education Committee of Students Against US Intervention in the Middle East, Ann Arbor, MI, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Phoukout Stronghold: Neo Lao Haksat Publications, Washington, DC, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Pig: The Peace & Freedom Party, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Plain Rapper: Palo Alto Resistance, Palo Alto, CA, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Ploughshare: Teachers Anti-War Movement, UK, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Plowshare Press: Center for Economic Conversion, Mountain View, CA, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 54, Box 23, Folder 22)
- Plowshare Press: Mid-Peninsula Conversion Project, San Francisco, CA, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Plowshares Newsletter: Plowshares Newsletter, Orlando, FL, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Political Programme of the South Vietnam National Front for Liberation: Students for a Democratic Society, Undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Post War World Council Newsletter: Post War World Council, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 56, Box 28, Folder 1)
- Potomac Alliance Power Plant: Potomac Alliance, Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Primal Scream: Primal Scream, Longmont, CO, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Proceedings of the Third US Congress Against War and Fascism: The American League Against War and Fascism, New York, NY, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Proceedings of US Congress Against War: US Congress Against War, New York, NY, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Professional: Professionals' Coalition for Nuclear Arms Control, Washington, DC, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Program & Legislative Action: Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, Philadelphia, PA, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
- Program of Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Vietnam Veterans Against the War, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
- PSR.NYC Newsletter: Physicians for Social Responsibility of New York City, New York, NY, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Psychologie života v terezínském koncentračním táboře, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Punji Stick: Liberation Support Movement, Berkeley, CA, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Quaker Service Bulletin: American Friends Service Committee, New York, NY, 1973 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 18)
- Quaker Service Bulletin: American Friends Service Committee, Philadelphia, PA, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1, Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 4-5)
- Queens Freeze: The Queens Nuclear Freeze, Flushing, NY, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Quest for Peace: Quixote Center, Hyattsville, MD, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 10, Box 28, Folder 2)
- Questions of Complicity and Responsibility: Vietnam Veterans United to Prevent World War III, New York, NY, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Questions & Answers About the Gulf War: Questions & Answers, San Francisco, CA, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Radioactive Fallout from a Single One Megaton Nuclear Weapon Detonated at Ground Level on Rayethon Waltham Plant: Council for a Livable World Education Fund, Boston, MA, Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Radish: Buffalo Peace and Freedom Party, Troy, NY, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Rainbow Newsletter: Rainbow Coalition, Boston, MA, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Rainbow Peace Festival Flyer: Root Press, Claro, Switzerland, Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Rampart Wall Poster: Ramparts Magazine, Inc., 1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Reality: The World's Spotlight on Germany: George Binney Dibblee, London, UK, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Relay-Inform: American Friends Service Committee (AFSC), New York, NY, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Report of Activities: Stockholm International Peace Research Institute, Stockholm, Sweden, 1969-1975 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Report of the Gould House Conference on Economics of Disarmament: Committee for World Development and World Disarmament/Post War World Council, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Report of the International Peace Congress held at The Hague under the auspices of the International Federation of Trade Unions: International Federation of Trade Unions, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Resist: National Anti-Draft Network, New York, NY, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Resistance: New England Resistance, Boston, MA, 1968-1986 (Box 24, Folder 2, Box 18, Folder 6)
- Resistance National Newsletter: Resistance National Newsletter, Undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Resistance News: National Resistance Committee, San Francisco, CA, 1984-1987 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Return Address: Moscow: International News Bulletin on Independent Peace Activity in the USSR: Group for Establishing Trust, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Ribbon: Ribbon, Inc., Denver, CO, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Rich Man's War, Poor Man's Fight: Cincinnati Workers Unity League, Cincinnati, OH, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Rocky Mountain Peace & Justice Center: Rocky Mountain Peace & Justice Center, Boulder, CO, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Salute: Vet Publishers, Inc., New York, NY, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Sane Voice: National Student Council for a Sane Nuclear Policy, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- SANE World: Newsletter of the Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy: Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, Washington, DC, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Sane/Freeze News: National Office of Sane/Freeze: Campaign for Global Security, Washington, DC, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 27, Box 24, Folder 6, Box 28, Folder 3)
- Santa Fe Hips Voice: New Mexico Research Library of the Southwest, Santa Fe, NM, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- SCAR News: Free Hand Press, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Second Conference: International Trade Union Committee for Solidarity with the Workers and People of Vietnam Against the U.S. Imperialist Aggressors, Hanoi, Vietnam, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Seeds of Change: Peace & Justice Education Center, Rochester, NY, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Servitude et Grandeur des Français: Scènes des Années Terribles: La Bibliotheque Française, France, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Seventeenth Strategy For Peace Conference Report: The Stanley Foundation, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 5)